LAWRENCE A-J **SORIANO**

0961 465 0542 📞

lawrence.dev25@gmail.com 🔀

Dasmariñas, Cavite •

ABOUT ME

I am a self-taught web developer with three years of experience creating user-friendly, responsive websites tailored to the needs of businesses and individuals. I focus on delivering high-quality, visually appealing solutions while staying up-to-date with the latest technologies to ensure effective results.

SKILLS

- WordPress
- Shopify
- HTML
- Github

- CSS
- JavaScript
- Spring boot Java
- Gitlab

- GraphQL
- Divi
- Elementor
- Postman

EXPERIENCE

Sep 2024 - Present Web Developer

Freelancer

- Build and optimize business WordPress themes to match brand identity with custom CSS.
- Customize and optimize the e-commerce website based on the client's
- Build and design charity WordPress website to increase donor engagement with seamless payment integration.
- Customize PNG charity WordPress website to amplify impact stories with immersive multimedia features

Dec 2023 - Sep 2024 Web Developer

JFK Software Solutions

- Build WordPress websites from scratch using Elementor and custom CSS
- Developed a professional business website on WordPress
- · Created a Shopify site for a clothing store
- Built a full CRUD system for data management
- Integrated a GraphQL API for smoother data handling
- Maintain both WordPress and Shopify websites

Nov 2022 - Aug 2023 Web Developer

CM Digital

- Develop and maintaining WordPress website
- Develop and maintaining Shopify website Using any page builder in
- WordPress Page speed optimization
- Handle domain and email migrations Fixing technical issues
- Set-up Google Tag Manager
- Set-up Google Analytics
- Set-up Google Search Console
- Set-up Google Google Business Profile

EDUCATION

2018-2020

Paliparan III SHS - CAVITE

2014 - 2018

DSSCS - Cavite

Senior High School

Graduated

High School

Graduated

REFERENCE

Francis Guerrero

Software Engineer JFK Software Solutions Phone: 0977 205 4027

Email: kaitech.francis@gmail.com